

MOA **STENQVIST**

NAME: Moa Stengvist **DATE OF BIRTH: 820913** ADDRESS: Bäckegatan 34A, 413 16 Göteborg PHONE: 0733-42 22 06 E-MAIL: moa@stonetwig.se



I'M GOOD AT:

- Fly airplanes
- O Drive a car
- Babysit
- Solve problems
- O Photograph
- Wrap gifts
- ✓ Interview

- **⊘** Write
- Bake buns
- Serve Guinness ◆

I used to

a bar on

Ireland.

- Plan strategies
- Driving trucks
- Chinese
- Negativity

I'm looking for employment/internship with a company where I can, under one roof, combine my two biggest passions in life; code and design. And contribute my experience and knowledge in these areas.

I AM CURRENTLY STUDYING to become a Front end developer at Medieinstitutet in Gothenburg and I definately feel that I have come to the right place. To really learn to code and program is the best thing I have ever done and I love problem solving. My interest in web development began eight years ago when I took a course in web design. Since then I have created many websites for customers and companies, both in Sweden and internationally.

I have worked as a graphic designer for about 14 years, which I benefit greatly from in my role as a web developer. I am also previously trained in UX and UI design and think that accessibility and the user perspective are important aspects in everything I create.

RIGHT AT THE BEGINNING of my career, I worked as a writer for one of Swedens' largest music magazines and later also for newspaper GT/ Expressen, with a culture/entertainment editorial focus. (I also have an education in journalism). The last 10 years I've been working as a graphic designer, web designer and writer for Stampen Media/OTV, Long Tall Sally PR and as self employd at my own company Stonetwig Design.

I'm committed, dedicated and put my soul into everything I do. In a professional role, I'm creative, efficient and

independent and I'm not afraid to work hard and intensively.

I HOPE AND BELIEVE, that if I get the chance to become a part of your staff, that I can be useful - not only as a front end developer - but also as a graphic designer, copywriter and UX/ UI designer.



Graphic Design. I created a cover for the Nintendo Switch game "Black Future '88" which is available for purchase in game stores around the world.



CURRICULUM VITAE

EXPERIENCE

NOWA KOMMUNIKATION AND LONG TALL SALLY:

February 2017 - ongoing. Art Director and writer, a collaboration on a freelance basis.

STAMPEN MEDIA/OTV:

February 2010 - August 2020. Project manager, Art Director, web designer, digital production, writer, editor, photographer.

SELF-EMPLOYED:

January 2009 - ongoing. Stonetwig Design. Graphic design, web design, writer.

ADAX MEDIA/DIREKTPRESS GÖTEBORG:

April 2009 - February 2010. Newspaper editing and advertisement production.

MEDIA-KONSULT I GBG AB:

June 2008 - December 2008. Art Director, editor and advertisement production. Launched the Hallå newspapers.

ANNONSMEDIA VÄST AB:

February 2006 - June 2008. Graphic designer and advertisement production.

KVÄLLSTIDNINGARNA GT/ EXPRESSEN:

Internship January - February 2005. Journalist, entertainment editorial staff. The internship period was followed by a temporary position.

COMPETENCE

HTML5/CSS3 Javascript WordPress

Adobe XD

Animate

InVision

Microsoft Office

Indesign

Illustrator

Photoshop

Premiere Pro

After Effects



Graphic design. The John Wick Hex game was announced at a major event in New York and received many awards during E3 in Los Angeles. I created a flyer for the event in New York and a big roll up that was on display during E3.



Graphic design och project management. Inbjudan till Bohuslän is an inspirational magazine published by tourism organizations in Bohuslän. In 2011, they made the procurement process a competition where various agencies were invited to submit proposals. My design won and the magazine became a recurring project for several years.



Web design. I created a new website for Jenson8, a company in London that offers a unique concept for team building and workshops. High demands were placed on creativity and originality:

www.jenson8.com



EDUCATION

FRONT END DEVELOPER:

Medieinstitutet Gothenburg, 2020-2022.

UX OCH GRÄNSSNITTSDESIGN:

UX/UI, intuitive interface for app and web Berghs School of Communication, autumn 2019.

DIPLOMERAD WEBBDESIGNER:

HTML5, CSS3, WordPress, Art College, Gothenburg, autumn 2013.

JOURNALISM:

Ljungskile folkhögskola, 2003-2005.

ENGLISH COMMUNICATION:

5p, Högskolan i Trollhättan/Uddevalla, 2003.